

☐ (+91) 9426754267 | ☐ riyay9594@gmail.com

Summary

Software Developer with 6+ months of experience, specializing in back-end/front-end technologies & have also worked as Quality Analyst. Looking forward to leveraging my skills and experience in a platform that encourages growth, innovation and provides an opportunity to contribute to the success of the company.

I am a highly motivated, positive and goal-oriented individual with an analytical approach.

Work Experience

Thomson Reuters Ahmedabad, India INTERN JAVA DEVELOPER /QUALITY ANALYST March. 2023 - PRESENT • Developed Functionalities in Cleardocs.

Infolabz IT Services Pvt.Ltd Ahmedabad, India DEVELOPER May. 2019 - April 2020 • Basic of Machine Learning and Data Mining using Python.

Infolabz IT Services Pvt.Ltd Ahmedabad, India DEVELOPER May. 2019 - April 2020 • Web Design with using PHP.

Major Projects

Cleardocs Thomson Reuters TAX AND ACCOUNTING MARCH 2023 - PRESENT 2023 • Developed Back-end and Front-end for one functionality.

Smart Residential System InfoLabz IT Services Pvt. Ltd. AI/ML JANUARY 2021 - JUNE 2021 • Developed Back-end and Front-end Using PHP.

Technical Skills

- Languages :: Java , JavaScript , Python ,
- Database :: PostgreSQL
- Others :: Web Development , RestApi , Microservices ,

Education

Adani Institute of Infrastructure & Engineering, Gujarat CGPA 8.20 BE. INFORMATION & COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY July. 2020 - may. 2023 •

Govt. Girls Polytechnic, Gujarat CGPA 8.79 Diploma Information Technology Jan. 2017 - July. 2020 •

Nelson High School, Gujarat 73.8% GSHSEB CLASS 10TH March. 2017

Social Links

• LinkedIn :: https://www.linkedin.com/in/riya-yadav-7790b7219